https://www.ccsnh.edu/ccsnh-privacy-statement/

Skip to content
Revised:  12/14/2012
Your Privacy Is Important To Us:
So you understand how the CCSNH protects your privacy we provide this statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this statement easy to find, we make it available on our web pages and where personally identifiable information may be requested.
Collected Information:
This statement applies to all information collected or submitted on the Community College System of New Hampshire website. On some pages, you may request information, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages can include:
NameAddressEmail addressPhone number(etc.)
You may also submit information about other people. The types of personal information collected can include:
NameAddressPhone Number(etc.)
How We Use Your Submitted Information:
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing a request only to complete that request. We do not share this information with outside parties except in cases where it is necessary to complete your request.
We use your return email address to answer your email. Email addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to inform our decisions about our website design and content.  This information is not used to disclose the identity of individuals.
We do not use information submitted to us in ways unrelated to what is outlined above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
The CCSNH Is Committed To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place policies, appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial controls to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Children’s Privacy:
The CCSNH does not knowingly collect information on our website from those who are under the age of 13.  Nor is this an age group which is targeted by our website design or content.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Personal Information
By contacting us directly you can:
See what has been collected about youCorrect factual errors
To protect your privacy and security, we will make reasonable efforts to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections on your behalf.
How To Contact Us
If you have questions or concerns about this privacy statement, please contact us by sending email to:
webmaster@ccsnh.edu
Still can’t find what you’re looking for? No problem.
SearchL
Search for:
X
COVID-19 Information
